My buddy sent a driver to pick us up
Now we will take this car from Baiyun Airport to my buddy's place
It will be about 4 hours
Hey bro, do you know about Huanong Brothers shooting videos?
I do
Yeah
They are local celebrities. Very famous
Yeah, celebrities
Both of you are Internet celebrities
Aiya, celebrity or not... It's like...
I don't think that's a big deal
We are all ordinary people
After a long journey, we've arrived at my buddy's place
As we can't visit with our hands empty
I've brought
Our home made rapeseed oil. Or "kuan you" ("wide oil")
And also one box of mooncake for each of my buddies
Now we are in front of their gate
Buddy!
You've arrived, buddy
Why did you take so much stuff
Come in please
This is the "kuan you" that I brought by myself
Take a seat inside
Wow, your dogs are so polite
These dogs don't bite
Hold this part (which is not hot)
These corns are taken from my brother's place
He has so many
Let's eat outside
Eat outside
You look blacker recently
Yeah, got a lot of sunlight recently
Let me introduce them
This is my uncle
A professional butcher
[laughters]
This is one of
our students
Hello, hello
Hello
You're so pretty
You're so pretty, too
[laughters]
That's mean you are really pretty
This corn tastes really good
Will I get a heatstroke after eating this corn?
No no no
These are all
All taken from my brother's place
By the way
Uncle said he wants to check out your bamboo rats
Sure
Introduce your bamboo rat
And last time...
How is that one...
How's the "Elizabeth" rat?
Pretty good. Still up over there
Fatter and fatter now
Let's go and chat
Yeah, let's go and chat
Yeah
Right up over there
The chickens also look good
All are hens
Eh, where are your pigs?
They're all locked up
Locked up?
Too naughty
They go outside and eat...
Eat other people's cabbages
Cabbages?
If they are unlocked, they go outside immediately
They're used to that
They often go outside when we're not here
They may...
They may become wild pigs if not locked
Or... just gone
That'll be a huge loss
[laughters]
The bamboo rats are so fat
Each male with two females
So huge
Now the male-to-female ratio is, 1 male to 7 females
Wouldn't the male rats be too exhausted?
I have no way. All the male rats are sold
Only a few are left
So they have to rotate
After one batch are pregnant, I'll take them away and put some others in
That's really hard work for the male rats
I've sold too much. There're not too many male rats left
And I don't want to sell the female ones
They can born new rats
These are
one-to-two or alike
I heard that your "Elizabeth" is very pretty. Can I take a look?
Over there
- Over there
- Let's take a look
Wow, so pretty
So pretty, for real
So pretty
I feel like... is he thinner than before?
No, no. This isn't "Elizabeth"
Oh
This doesn't have a name
"Namelessabeth"
[laughters]
It's still white
But really naughty
Naughty means dangerous
Look, it's like a bunny
See, I can hold him like this and he doesn't move at all
So gentle
Male or female?
Male
Really so gentle
He doesn't bite at all
The other one bites
This is so gentle
So gentle
Can even hug him like this
Come on, say hi to the crowd
Hello. It's been a year since we met last time. I missed you so much
He doesn't speak
He must want to say "hello everybody"
Um... Do white rats taste differently from black rats?
I have no idea
[laughters]
White rats don't taste good
Wow you dodged it
This is Xi Xi
Xi Xi
I assigned Xi Xi as his wife now
Oh
So their babies will be white
Is it a genetic mutation?
Yeah, a genetic mutation
The whole body is white
They bite
You gotta watch it. Their teeth are very sharp
Don't touch around. They may bite you
If you want to touch it, raise it in the tail
Even this little one bites
Even little ones bite?
The little one is so cute
Look, its teeth are still white. Haven't turned yellow yet
Right. Not yellow yet
They'll turn yellow slowly
It's still having milk. Not weaned yet
Can I hold it?
Hold it in the tail
Watch out. It turns around and bites you
Don't throw and hurt it
No worries. It can't turn around
Wow it's so adorable
Now it wants to bite you
It's angry now
So gentle. The little one
Hold it like this so it can't bite me
It doesn't bite you?
It can't. Pinch it here with your hand
It's like, you've pinched its neck
Pinch its neck so it can't turn around. It's not that strong
Bigs rats can't be pinched like this. I don't even dare
Big rats are much stronger
Even you feel scary of the big ones, do you?
I do. Even for me
I got bitten sometimes
I've been bitten for a few times this year
Anyway, I got bitten in every year
If I clap my hands, are they going to be quiet?
Wow. Amazing!
They heard the sound
They thought danger is coming. So they get down and stop moving
They are scared
And slowly they'll restart
They've restarted now
Suddenly it was quiet
Yeah, suddenly it's quiet
Amazing
Let's try beating the bamboo
"Bang!" and then suddenly it's all quiet
- Is there any bamboo?
- Yes, over there
Let's beat it
Two of them didn't listen
Over there
Everyone be quiet! The meeting has started!
Still two noisy ones over there
I beat bamboo too often, so they are not very scared
They are used to it, so they are not scared
They'll be very scared when not very used to it
These are not weaned yet
Do they fight when they are little?
Nope
They don't fight when they are little?
Not even after they grow up, as long as they are not put together
Do they fight only when fight for a wife?
Eh, no. They fight only after giving birth
Oh, protecting the kids
Yeah. It's an instinct
Even if you put a lot of them together, they don't fight
These pigs are very expensive in our place
- Very expensive
- Yeah
25 yuan for a jin (500g)
25 yuan for a jin
Yeah
25 yuan each jin for what?
This pork. 25 yuan for each jin.
Oh
Give them some more water
These pigs don't grow big. Very hard to grow big
They are probably only 20 jin now
If you sell them in our place, it will be...
probably over 1000 yuan
These little pigs are six or seven hundred yuan
They grow too slowly
We feed them with only vegetable leaves and elephant grass leaves
Your pigs look so spiritual
Yeah
Do these pigs taste better?
Better for sure
They are fed with grass
with vegetable leaves everyday
Oh
Have you thought of having a little pig to eat some time?
Hmm... I raised them by myself. Don't quite want to eat
I won't eat before they grow big
There are bigs ones. A big one over there
That's the male pig
If I kill the male pig
That's the daddy of the little pigs. What if all of them attack me?
You can kill them all
[laughters]
You are so cruel
You can kill them all, and then no one hates you
Where are we going now? For the fish
It's on the hill
Oh, is that yours?
Yeah. That's my own pond
There's a lot of fish in it
Now, it's like...
One year without taking out the fish
Yeah
Let's catch some fish, over there.
Then I'll shut down and stop recording
Sure, sure